dpshots.com 2010-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Digital Photography Shots

Your privacy is critically important to us. At DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) we have a few fundamental principles:

We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)

We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. Like we might store information of User Behavior on our site so that we can tweak the User Interface of our site accordingly.

We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. DPShots ( http://dpshots.com )’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how DPShots ( http://dpshots.com )’s visitors use its website. From time to time, DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to DPShots ( http://dpshots.com )’s websites choose to interact with DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) in ways that require DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. However, DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Aggregated Statistics

DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) may monitor thethe User Behavior on DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ).com, like what visitors View, what they click on etc. DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on DPShots ( http://dpshots.com )’s behalf or to provide services available at DPShots ( http://dpshots.com )’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using DPShots ( http://dpshots.com )’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ), third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) website and have supplied your email address, DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) uses cookies to help DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) identify and track visitors, their usage of DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) website, and their website access preferences. DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using DPShots ( http://dpshots.com )’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of DPShots ( http://dpshots.com )’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in DPShots ( http://dpshots.com )’s sole discretion. DPShots ( http://dpshots.com ) encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
